{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question": "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National 'What' Service?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Humanity"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Health"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Honour"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Household"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Pocahontas"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Sleeping Beauty"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Cinderella"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Elsa"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim? ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Hangar"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Terminal"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Concourse"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Carousel"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": "Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Phillips"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Flymo"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Chubb"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Ronseal"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Republicanism"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Communism"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Conservatism"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Liberalism"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question": "Which toys have been marketed with the phrase 'Robots in Disguise'?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Bratz Dolls"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Sylvanian Families"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Hatchimals"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Transformers"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question": "What does the word loquacious mean?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Angry"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Chatty"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Beautiful"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Shy"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question": "Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Childbirth"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Broken bones"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Heart conditions"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Old age"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question": "Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Ramadan"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Diwali"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Lent"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Hanukkah"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question": "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Bahamas"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "US Virgin Island"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Turks and Caicos Islands"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Bermuda"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "11",
            "question": "Who is the only British politician to have held all four 'Great Offices of State' at some point during their career?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "David Lloyd George"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Harold Wilson"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "James Callaghan"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "John Major"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "12",
            "question": "In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "A",
                    "leter": "A",
                    "option": "Calico Jack"
                },
                {
                    "id": "B",
                    "leter": "B",
                    "option": "Blackbeard"
                },
                {
                    "id": "C",
                    "leter": "C",
                    "option": "Bartholomew Roberts"
                },
                {
                    "id": "D",
                    "leter": "D",
                    "option": "Captain Kidd"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    "answers": [
        {
            "id" : "1",
            "answer" : ["B"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "2",
            "answer" : ["C"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "3",
            "answer" : ["D"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "4",
            "answer" : ["C"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "5",
            "answer" : ["B"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "6",
            "answer" : ["D"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "7",
            "answer" : ["B"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "8",
            "answer" : ["A"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "9",
            "answer" : ["B"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "10",
            "answer" : ["A"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "11",
            "answer" : ["C"]
        },
        {
            "id" : "12",
            "answer" : ["B"]
        }
    ],
    "prizes": [
        "$500",
        "$1,000",
        "$2,000",
        "$4,000",
        "$8,000",
        "$16,000",
        "$32,000",
        "$64,000",
        "$125,000",
        "$250,000",
        "$500,000",
        "$1,000,000"
    ]
}